

PROFIL

I decided last year to reorient myself as a web developer after working in the hospitality industry for 10 years. I chose this field because I find it very interesting and limitless. I am very motivated to improve my skills with you.

PERSONAL INFOS



(+43)6 76 620 50 46



jimmybakerchaves@gmail.com



jimmy.codefactory.live



Hetzendorfer Straße 112 VIENNA 1120(AUSTRIA)

Geb. Datum 25.05.1988

Staatsbürgerschaft France

JIMMY CHAVES

Web Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

06 / 2023 - 09/2023

Web Developer (Internship)

CNS-Solutions GmbH, Vienna (Austria)

Development of the new Website (in process)

02 / 2022 - 08 / 2022

Cook

Hotel INDIGO Vienna, Vienna (Austria)

09 / 2020 - 02 / 2022

Baker

Paremi, Wien (Austria)

06 / 2012 - 02 / 2022

Baker

In different bakeries, restaurants,... (France, Ireland, ...)

AUSBILDUNG

08 / 2022 - 12 / 2022 Fullstack Web Developer Cerificate Code Factory Vienna

01 / 2012 - 06 / 2012 Bäcker Zertifikate

IMT Grenoble (France)

09 / 2006 - 06 / 2008 High School Diploma (Mathematics)

Lycee A.Berges (France)

SKILLS

HTML

CSS/SCSS

Javascript

PHP

Bootstrap

RestAPI

Problem Solving

LANGUAGES

French
German
English
Slovak

REFERENCES

CODE FACTORY VIENNA +43 6 99 12255185

CNS-Solutions & Support GmbH office@cns-solutions.net

VOLUNTEER WORK

04 / 2015 - 12 / 2015 Volunteer in a gipsy's kindergarden YMCA (Slovakia)

HOBBYS

Travel

Sports

New technologies

Cook / Bake